SHELDON: I'm glad to see
you made it safely.
(Sheldon:)How's your hotel?
(Amy(on Skype):)It's not the best Best Western
I've been to,
(Amy(on Skype):)but I'd say it's...
(Amy(on Skype):)the third best Best Western
I've been to.
(Sheldon:)I know how you feel.
(Sheldon:)The Best Buy by my house
is only the third best Best Buy.
(Sheldon:)They have
the best buys,
(Sheldon:)but having the best buys
isn't the only thing
(Sheldon:)that makes a Best Buy
the best Best Buy.
(Amy:)What makes a best Best Buy
the best Best Buy?
(Sheldon:)Mm, that's a great question.
(Sheldon:)I like when they're
next to a Chipotle.
(Amy:)Okay, well, I should unpack.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Enjoy the neurobiology
conference.
(Amy:)I will.
(Amy:)I... wish you were here.
(Sheldon:)At a neurobiology conference?
(Sheldon:)What a mean thing to say.
Okay, I'm glad you're not here?
(Sheldon:)Aw, you always know
just what to say
(Sheldon:)after I tell you what to say.
(Amy:)Good-bye, Sheldon.